And I do not have other title information, but I will develop a variant title to put the title in original writing instead.
Like this.
So
And I have no filing values to take into account.
I also write the origin information in translated form as it says on the title page.
Next is a circulation task and there is rarely information about editions in new books
But if there is information then we will take it as it looks in the manifestation.
And here I actually have, and it looks like this.
So there.
Publication.
The first feature of primary publication is land.
And since we start from a template, Sweden is already managed
But we know that this manifestation comes from Serbia.
Publishing time is a nuclear element for published manifestations
Year may only contain four alphanumeric characters.
It is not uncommon for the actual publication year to be in the book.
The publication year can be based on the print year or the Cophyright year.
We have a print year and copyright year which is 2019.
Date is used if we do not have a secure publication year in the book and then need to specify characters other than those that are allowed in the capacity year.
In this case, we base the release on the print year and therefore need to enter 2019 within staples.
So
Then we have manufacturing.
Since we have based the publication on the print year, we need to specify that year without staples in manufacturing.
We don't really need to fill in the place and agent, but we do it now.
So, here it should say ... so.
But as I said, most libraries do not have to care about the manufacturing tasks.
Range
Then we enter the last paginated page.